g3fashions.in 2019-06-29

# Privacy Policy | G3 Fashion is the Best Place to Shop Online Indian Ethnic Wear for All

## Use of Personal Information.

G3fashion.com collects personally identifiable information from the visitors to our website. Personal information collected may include name, email address, postal address with zip/pin code, shipping | billing address login ID - password and contact number. This information is collected if you request information from us, participate in a contest or sweepstakes, and signup to join our email list or request some other service or information from us. We never use any customer related information for commercial usages.

We will collect information also about at where you are on the internet (e.g. the URL from you are visiting, IP address, domain details), your browser type, location of country, visited pages details of G3 fashion.com website at the time of visiting, the advertisements you clicked on. We may collect this information even if you do not register with us. None of this data is of a personal nature and will help us improve the quality of our service.

We require these details only to provide you the services we offer. We use your address to deliver the order. We may use your phone number to help you resolve your queries while shopping. We notify you about our updates and promotional schemes through SMS or email on your mobile number/ email ID provided to us during the time of registration. You can inform us if you wish to stop receiving these mailers. We share your personal information with specific employees who are involved in the execution of your transaction and any employee who violates our privacy and/or security policies is subject to disciplinary action.

## Non-Personal Information

In some cases, we may collect information about you that is not personally identifiable. We use this information-which does not identify individual users, it is solely used to analyses trends and administer the site, to track users' movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. The information collected is used solely for internal review and not shared.

## Customer Reviews and Testimonials :

We will use all the testimonials and reviews given by customer on our web site which may contain personally identifiable information. If you would like to have your testimonial or review removed from our site, you have to mail us on customercare@g3fashion.com

## Card Information :

For all online transactions information is securely collected by relevant payment gateways. Our payment gateways are dedicated to keeping your account safe and secure. With the industries advanced encryption, fraud prevention and protection policies, once your information reaches our payment gateways it resides on a server of payment gateways that are heavily guarded both physically and electronically.

## Announcements regarding services of G3 Fashions.in

We will mail / SMS for site updating to our customers by using our data base. We ask for a user’s email address for the purposes of providing this information. If personal identifiable information changes or If you don’t want to receive any update from us. You can email us customercare@g3fashion.com. If you don’t want the details, you can deactivate your account.

## Service Providers

We use other third parties such as a shipping company and a payment gateway company to bill you for goods and services. We are using live chat option to assist you for customer’s queries / questions while using our site related queries or regarding your order. When you will sign up in G3 Fashion, we will share your provided personal information as essential for the third party to provide that service.

## Legal Disclaimer

We reserve the right to disclose your personal recognizable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site. G3fashion reserves the right to make changes in this privacy policy.

## Agreeing to Terms

If you do not agree to G3 fashion Privacy Policy as posted here on this website, please do not use this site or any services offered by this site. Your use of this site indicates acceptance of this privacy policy.

We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies only to information collected by this Web site.
